https://foamtapes.net/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
About UsBuyers GuidesCustomer ReviewsShipping & PoliciesFoam Tape LingoReturn PolicyQuality PolicyShop AllGasket TapeBuyer's Guide: Closed Cell Gasket TapePolyethylene Foam TapeNeoprene Sponge TapePVC Foam Tape3M™ Extreme Sealing TapeFoam Sealant TapeCork TapeWeatherstripping TapeBuyer's Guide: Weatherstripping TapeBuyer's Guide: Open Cell Foam TapeEther Foam TapeEster Foam TapeReticulated Filter FoamFelt TapeFoam Weatherseal TapeWindow Insulation BundleDouble Sided TapeBuyer's Guide: Double Sided Foam TapesWhite Foam Mounting TapeFoam Mounting SquaresVery High Bond Acrylic Tape45 mil High Bond Tape25 mil High Bond TapeClear High Bond TapeExtreme Environment TapeGlazing TapeMarkets & ApplicationsPPE Personal Protective EquipmentStud & Joist IsolationPVC Foam Joist Tape & Drywall SoundproofingNeoprene Rubber Joist & Drywall Soundproof TapeWindow & DoorGlazing TapeSDL Muntin TapeReticulated Filter Foam & BafflesFlashing Tape3M™ All Weather Flashing Tape 8067Flashing Tape Installation GuideSqueak Reduction & Anti Rattle TapesGlass & MirrorCork Transportation PadsBlue Separator PadsGlazing TapeAutomotiveAutomotive Tape - V1500 - 15# Black PVCAutomotive Tape - V710/V700 - 7# Black PVC TapeSurface ProtectionBumpersCross Reference ChartFIRESALE!Contact UsCustomer ServiceTrouble Placing an Order?Returns Policy
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
Privacy Statement
Foamtapes.net is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Foamtapes.net Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Foamtapes.net website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Foamtapes.net collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Foamtapes.net also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Foamtapes.net. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Foamtapes.net for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Foamtapes.net Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Foamtapes.net public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Foamtapes.net does not read any of your private online communications.
Foamtapes.net encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Foamtapes.net so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Foamtapes.net is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Foamtapes.net and Foamtapes.net family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Foamtapes.net collects and uses your personal information to operate the Foamtapes.net Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Foamtapes.net also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Foamtapes.net and its affiliates. Foamtapes.net may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Foamtapes.net does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Foamtapes.net may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Foamtapes.net may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Foamtapes.net, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Foamtapes.net does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Foamtapes.net keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Foamtapes.net, in order to determine what Foamtapes.net services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Foamtapes.net to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Foamtapes.net Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Foamtapes.net or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Foamtapes.net; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Foamtapes.net, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Foamtapes.net Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Foamtapes.net pages, or register with Foamtapes.net site or services, a cookie helps Foamtapes.net to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Foamtapes.net Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Foamtapes.net features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Foamtapes.net services or Web sites you visit.
Foamtapes.net uses Google Adwords tracking cookies for remarketing. This means you may see ads from us on other websites that are part of the Google Content Network (GCN). This allows us to continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service. As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system. You may opt out of this technology at any time by using Google's opt out feature
Security of your Personal Information
Foamtapes.net secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Foamtapes.net secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Foamtapes.net will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Foamtapes.net encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Foamtapes.net is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Foamtapes.net welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Foamtapes.net has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Foamtapes.net at noreply@foamtapes.net. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Compare Products
Remove This Item
Compare
Clear All
You have no items to compare.
Copyright © 2020 Foamtapes.net, a division of LAMATEK, Inc. All rights reserved.
